// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'Who has been growing heirloom and goth tomatoes in their garden?', 
      a: 'West', 
      b: 'Perica',
      c: 'David',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been baking and eating tons of sugar cookies?', 
      a: 'Darice', 
      b: 'Jenn',
      c: 'Marcus',
      d: 'Jenni',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has become an expert at making homemade pasta and pizza?', 
      a: 'ChelseA', 
      b: 'Sarah',
      c: 'Archana',
      d: 'Autumn',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been perfecting the Kale Caesar Salad?', 
      a: 'Nick B.', 
      b: 'Kendra',
      c: 'Kellee',
      d: 'Lynn',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been smoking foods like a BBQ Pit Master?', 
      a: 'Brady', 
      b: 'Ryan',
      c: 'Geoff',
      d: 'David',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been playing the puzzle game Limbo?', 
      a: 'Libby', 
      b: 'Sean',
      c: 'Haley',
      d: 'Tay',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been golfing and playing Call of Duty?', 
      a: 'Tyler', 
      b: 'Geoff',
      c: 'Brady',
      d: 'Chris',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been striking some super chill yoga poses?', 
      a: 'Molly', 
      b: 'Phillip',
      c: 'Joelle',
      d: 'Josh',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been getting crafty with Origami?', 
      a: 'Lynn', 
      b: 'Archana',
      c: 'Melissa',
      d: 'Jalalala',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who has been ranking film franchises?', 
      a: 'James', 
      b: 'John',
      c: 'West',
      d: 'Jalalala',
      answer: 'b'
    }
  ]
};